<resources>
    <string name="app_name">aCapNYS</string>
    <string name="take_photo">Take Photo</string>
    <string name="start_capture">Start Capture</string>
    <string name="stop_capture">Stop Capture</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "1：眼振を撮影するためにスマホを眼前に固定する装具が必要です。\nバックカメラを利用するときは左上写真のような透明のプラスチックケースが使えます。"
        "粘着ゲルテープでスマホをケースに固定しています。フロントカメラの場合は慣れれば手で固定することも可能ですが、右上写真のような簡単な固定具を自作すると"
        "ブレの少ない眼振が撮れます。"
        "\n\n2：眼振の録画\nまず、使用するカメラを選択し、ズームを設定しておきます。"
        "\n〇録画開始：画面の中央の録画スタートボタンをタップ\n〇録画終了：画面の中央部分をタップ\nで録画完了です。"
        "\n右リストの項目をタップするとそれを再生し、長押しすると削除出来ます。"
        <!--        "\n\n3：右上隅の [Gyro] ボタンをタップすると、スマホの pitch, roll, yaw の動きをチェックしてアラームを鳴らし、回数を表示します。前庭リハビリのための機能です。"
-->
        "\n\n3：[Gyro]画面で、Windows アプリ CapNYS が指定する IP-Address, Port を設定すると、ジャイロデータを WiFi でその CapNYS に送信できます。"
        "Windows用 CapNYS は https://kuroda33.com/jibika からダウンロード出来ます。\n"
        "         "
    </string>
    <string name="eng_text">
        "1: A brace is required to hold the phone in front of the eye to capture the nystagmus.\n"
        "When using the back camera, a clear plastic case like the one pictured above left can be used."
        "Adhesive gel tape is used to secure the phone to the case. For the front camera, "
        "it is possible to fix the camera by hand if you are used to it, but if you make your own simple fixing device like"
        "the one shown in the upper right photo, you can take nystagmus with less blurring."
        "\n\n2: Recording Nystagmus\n"
        "* First, select the camera to be used and set the zoom.\n"
        "* Start recording: Tap the Start Recording button in the center of the screen.\n"
        "End recording: Tap the center of the screen.\n"
        "These two operations complete the recording.\n"
        "Tap an item in the list on the right side of the screen to play it. Press and hold to delete the item."
        <!--     "\n\n3: Tap the [Gyro] button in the upper right corner to check your phone's pitch, roll, and yaw movements, "
        "sound an alarm, and display the number of times. This function is for vestibular rehabilitation."
    -->
        "\n\n3: On the [Gyro] screen, you can set the IP-Address and Port specified by the Windows app CapNYS to send gyro data to that CapNYS via WiFi."
        "CapNYS for Windows can be downloaded from https://kuroda33.com/jibika."
        "     "
    </string>
    <string name="permissionText">
        "  \n"
        "      aCapNYSにカメラ、ファイルとメディア、マイクに対する権限を与えると\n"
        "      aCapNYSが動きます。下記の手順で権限を与えてください。\n\n"
        "　１：Android画面にもどって、設定（歯車アイコン）\n"
        "　２：アプリと通知\n"
        "　３：aCapNYS を探して、それをタップ\n"
        "　４：権限\n"
        "　　　カメラ、ファイルとメディア、マイクの３個をタップして、すべて許可\n"


    </string>
    <string-array name="spinner_items1">
        <item>OFF</item>
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>C</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="spinner_items2">
        <item>OFF</item>
        <item>S</item>
        <item>M</item>
        <item>L</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="video_files">
        <item>OFF34</item>
        <item>S3224</item>
        <item>M3134</item>
        <item>L1141</item>
        <item>OFF34</item>
        <item>S3224</item>
        <item>M3134</item>
        <item>L1141</item>
        <item>OFF34</item>
        <item>S3224</item>
        <item>M3134</item>
        <item>L1141</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>